(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1ST LIVE OVERTURE
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment for the performance to begin.
OVERTURE
嗚呼...
Ah...
水底と天井の隙間
The gap between the bottom and the surface
見下ろした三日月も笑って
Even the crescent moon looking down is laughing
無頓着なセンチメントだって
Even indifferent sentiments
包み隠すねいびいぶるう
Are hidden by navy blue
さあ 終わらない
Now, the never-ending...
夜をあける
...night breaks.
終わらない
Never-ending...
夜をあける
...night breaks.
終わらない
Never-ending...
夜をあける
...night breaks.
君だけの
Only for you...
夜をあける
...the night breaks.
静寂を切り裂いた轟音
A roar that tore through the silence
幕がひらいていく
The curtain is rising
声だけ聞こえてる　聞こえてる　聞こえてる
I only hear your voice... echoing... echoing...
声が聞こえてる　向こうから
I hear your voice from across the way.
頭に響いたアラートを辿って
I follow the alert ringing in my head,
今
right now.
空は騒いでる　騒いでる
The sky is roaring, roaring...
未確認昼のワンページ
An unidentified afternoon's page.
アレグロ背負って　駆け出して
Carrying 'Allegro' on my back, I start running,
さあ
now!
S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O
青星背に宣戦布告だ
Declaring war with the blue star at my back.
もう向かっている　向かっている
I'm already on my way, on my way.
さあ
Now!
S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O
現状前衛絶体絶命さ
Currently in the vanguard, a desperate situation.
撃っていけ　撃っていけ
Keep firing, keep firing.
あー
Ah!
波に飲まれるな　飲まれるな
Don't get swallowed by the waves... don't get swallowed.
波に飲まれるな　声を出せ
Don't get swallowed by the waves, raise your voice!
彼方で光ったポイント目掛けて
Aiming for the point shining in the distance,
今
right now.
空は騒いでる　騒いでる
The sky is roaring, roaring...
規格外ゲノム　トランジション
An extraordinary genome transition.
アレグロ背負って　負けなしで
Carrying 'Allegro' on my back, without losing,
さあ
now!
僕の番だ
It's my turn.
S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O
青星背に宣戦布告だ
Declaring war with the blue star at my back.
もう向かっている　向かっている
I'm already on my way, on my way.
さあ
Now!
S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O-S-O
現状前衛絶体絶命さ
Currently in the vanguard, a desperate situation.
撃っていけ　撃っていけ
Keep firing, keep firing.
抗っていけ　笑ったまま
Keep resisting, with a smile.
さあ
Now!
歌っていけ
Keep singing.
さあ
Now!
みなさん、初めましてー！
Nice to meet you all!
今日は私たちMidnight Grand Orchestra 1st LIVE「Overture」に
Thank you very much for joining our
ご参加いただき、誠にありがとうございます。
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st LIVE "Overture" today.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you.
イェーイ、みんな見えてる？イェーイ！
Yay! Can everyone see me? Yay!
えー、Midnight Grand Orchestraとは、私、星街すいせいと
So, Midnight Grand Orchestra is a musical unit formed
タク・イノウエさんが中心となって結成された音楽ユニットで、
primarily by myself, Hoshimachi Suisei, and Taku Inoue-san.
先月、7月27日にですね、デビューミニアルバム
Last month, on July 27th,
『Overture』をVIA/TOY'S FACTORYさんからリリースさせていただき、
we released our debut mini-album "Overture" from VIA/TOY'S FACTORY.
そのメジャーデビュー記念ライブということで、本日、この、
And today, as our major debut anniversary live, from this
超超超超超超超豪華なミドグラ専用ステージから、
super, super, super, super gorgeous MGO-exclusive stage,
最高の音楽を皆さまにお届けできればと思っております！
we hope to deliver the best music to all of you!
いや、めちゃくちゃ豪華っすね。
Man, it really is incredibly gorgeous.
いや、すごいですよ。
Yeah, it's amazing.
居心地はどうですか？
How are you feeling up here?
最高です！
It's the best!
イェーイ！ということでですね、えー、YouTubeのチラ見せ配信は
Yay! And so, the sneak peek broadcast on YouTube
なんと、ここまでとなってしまいます！YouTubeの皆さま、大変申し訳ございません。ここでお別れです。
ends right here! Everyone on YouTube, we're very sorry. It's time to say goodbye.
えー、このライブのね、とてつもない感じが結構伝わったんじゃないかなと思いますので、
I think the incredible atmosphere of this live performance came through,
ぜひね、気になった方はSPWNの方で最後まで一緒に盛り上がっていただけたら嬉しいです！
so if you're interested, we'd be happy if you'd join us on SPWN and get hyped until the very end!
ぜひぜひ、お願いします。
Please do, we'd love to have you.
ではね、今日は伝説のライブになること間違いなしなので、ぜひ最後まで見てください！
Well then, today is sure to be a legendary live performance, so please watch until the end!
皆さん！もっともっと盛り上がっていきましょう！
Everyone! Let's get more and more excited!
次のご機嫌なナンバーを聴いてください。
Please listen to the next upbeat number.
アレグロ
Allegro
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st LIVE OVERTURE